lacasting.com 2017-06-06

# 

Effective Date - lacasting.com and castingnetworks.com: April 26, 2016

Effective Date - sfcasting.com: May 23, 2016

**Privacy Policy Highlights**

These highlights detail important information regarding the collection, use, and sharing of information when you use the Services of Casting Networks, Inc. Please read our [full Privacy Policy](http://cni.lacasting.com/wsdl/webservice.svc/GetCurrentPolicy?siteId=LA&policyType=Privacy%20Policy#FullPP) for details and defined terms.

**Personal Information Collected** ****

Our Services include networking and database services. You understand that by using our Services you are choosing to provide personal and/or sensitive information about yourself and your work experience and that personal information you provide may be included in your posted Resume. We may also collect information about you from third-party service providers and the social networks you connect to. [More Info](http://cni.lacasting.com/wsdl/webservice.svc/GetCurrentPolicy?siteId=LA&policyType=Privacy%20Policy#collect)

**Tracking Technologies (Cookies, etc.)** ****

We use tracking technologies to automatically collect information from you on our Services relating to your use of our Services. If you access our Services through a mobile device, we might also collect additional information such as a unique device identifier and location information. When you use our Services, other parties such as third-party advertising partners and analytics providers may also collect information about your online activity. We do not track members in order to serve targeted advertising and therefore do not respond to “do-not-track” technology. [More Info](http://cni.lacasting.com/wsdl/webservice.svc/GetCurrentPolicy?siteId=LA&policyType=Privacy%20Policy#tracking)

**Use and Sharing of Information** ****

We may use and share information we collect from you to operate, improve, and personalize our Services. Your personal information may also be shared with marketing partners, affiliated companies, our service providers, mobile carriers, social networks, legal and law enforcement, and others if there is a change of control. Certain personal information entered in your Account Profile is automatically pulled from and displayed on your Resume. [More Info](http://cni.lacasting.com/wsdl/webservice.svc/GetCurrentPolicy?siteId=LA&policyType=Privacy%20Policy#use)

**Your California Privacy Rights** ****

If you are a California resident, you have additional rights. [More Info](http://cni.lacasting.com/wsdl/webservice.svc/GetCurrentPolicy?siteId=LA&policyType=Privacy%20Policy#california)

**Your Choices and Opt-Out** ****

Due to the nature of our Services, you have limited choices for restricting access to your personal information posted on your Resume. You may decline to provide us with personal information but this may limit or prevent you from setting up an account and participating in the Services. If you want to update your personal information or no longer want our Services, you may access your account and make the changes desired or you may contact us at [support@castingnetworks.com](mailto:support@castingnetworks.com). You may opt-out of receiving promotional communications from us. [More Info](http://cni.lacasting.com/wsdl/webservice.svc/GetCurrentPolicy?siteId=LA&policyType=Privacy%20Policy#choices)

**Arbitration** ****

Any disputes under this Privacy Policy will be resolved in accordance with the binding arbitration process outlined in the [Terms of Use](http://cni.castingnetworks.com/wsdl/webservice.svc/GetCurrentPolicy?siteId=NY&policyType=Talent%20Terms%20Of%20Use).

**Changes to this Privacy Policy** ****

Your notification that changes to this Privacy Policy have been made will be conveyed by our posting a new “Effective Date” on the Privacy Policy. [More Info](http://cni.lacasting.com/wsdl/webservice.svc/GetCurrentPolicy?siteId=LA&policyType=Privacy%20Policy#changes)

**Contact Us** ****

Questions about our Privacy Policy or about our handling of your information may be sent to [privacy@castingnetworks.com](mailto:privacy@castingnetworks.com). [More Info](http://cni.lacasting.com/wsdl/webservice.svc/GetCurrentPolicy?siteId=LA&policyType=Privacy%20Policy#contact)

Effective Date - lacasting.com and castingnetworks.com: April 26, 2016

Effective Date - sfcasting.com: May 23, 2016

**CASTING NETWORKS PRIVACY POLICY**

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY AND IN ITS ENTIRETY BEFORE USING OUR SERVICES. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE OUR SERVICES.

Casting Networks, Inc. (“CNI” “we” “our” or “us”) provides a range of content hosting, database and communication services to actors, models, dancers, voice-over actors and other artists (collectively, “Talent”) and connects Talent with agents and managers, casting directors, and others involved in motion picture, theatrical, radio, television and other entertainment enterprises (collectively, "Industry Professionals"). AS A RESULT OF THE TYPE OF NETWORKING SERVICES WE PROVIDE, YOU SHOULD NOT EXPECT THAT THE INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE WHEN USING OUR SERVICES WILL REMAIN PRIVATE. By accessing and using our Services, you are accepting the terms of this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) which govern our use of your information and our Terms of Use (“Terms”) [located here](http://cni.castingnetworks.com/wsdl/webservice.svc/GetCurrentPolicy?siteId=NY&policyType=Talent%20Terms%20Of%20Use), which govern your use of our Services and are incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy.

1\. ACCEPTANCE OF POLICY

This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the collection, use, and protection of information collected on our websites, mobile websites, mobile applications, and services that link to this Privacy Policy, or when you interact with CNI by any method of communication such as email, telephone, SMS, or in person in connection with the Services (collectively, "Services"). CNI provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use the Services and the choices we offer to manage the information we collect. Each time you use the Services, you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy. We will update this Privacy Policy with a new Effective Date to reflect changes in our collection and handling of personal information, which take effect immediately upon posting.

2\. SPECIAL NOTICES

YOU UNDERSTAND THAT BY USING OUR SERVICES YOU ARE AFFIRMATIVELY AND VOLUNTARILY CHOOSING TO PROVIDE PERSONAL AND/OR SENSITIVE INFORMATION ABOUT YOURSELF AND YOUR WORK EXPERIENCE AND THAT CERTAIN PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE INCLUDED IN YOUR RESUME (AS DEFINED IN SECTION 3 BELOW). YOUR RESUME IS SEARCHABLE ON THE SERVICES BY REGISTERED CASTING DIRECTORS, YOUR AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVES AND, IF YOU ARE PARTICIPATING IN _TALENT SCOUT,_ REGISTERED TALENT AGENTS AND MANAGERS (COLLECTIVELY, “INDUSTRY PROFESSIONALS”).  YOUR RESUME MAY BE MADE AVAILABLE OUTSIDE THE SERVICE BY YOU, YOUR AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE, OR INDUSTRY PROFESSIONALS ELECTRONICALLY BY EMAIL OR BY SHARING THE URL OF THE PAGE ON WHICH YOUR RESUME IS POSTED, OR FOUND BY WEB SEARCH ENGINES, WHICH ARE OUTSIDE OF OUR CONTROL. ONCE YOUR RESUME IS SHARED OR ACCESSIBLE VIA A SEARCH ENGINE, IT IS SUBJECT TO REDISTRIBUTION BY ANY THIRD PARTY THAT HAS ACCESS TO THE INFORMATION AND WE HAVE NO CONTROL OVER HOW OTHERS MAY USE YOUR RESUME OR THE INFORMATION CONTAINED IN IT. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU ARE AWARE OF ANY AND ALL RISKS INHERENT IN POSTING AND SHARING YOUR RESUME AS DESCRIBED AND BY DOING SO YOU ARE WILLING TO ASSUME THESE RISKS.

Authorized Representatives’ Access to Our Services

IF YOU HAVE AN AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE (DEFINED BELOW), YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOUR AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE HAS THE ABILITY TO CREATE AN ACCOUNT FOR YOU AND FULL ACCESS TO VIEW AND EDIT YOUR ACCOUNT PROFILE (AS DEFINED IN SECTION 3 BELOW) INFORMATION, SOME OF WHICHWILL BE UPLOADED INTO YOUR RESUME. IF AN AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE NO LONGER HAS THE AUTHORITY TO ACT ON YOUR BEHALF, IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO NOTIFY US TO UNLINK YOUR ACCOUNT AND/OR LINK YOUR ACCOUNT TO ANOTHER AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE. PLEASE NOTE THAT WE DO NOT TAKE STEPS TO CONFIRM IN ANY WAY THAT AN AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE HAS OBTAINED YOUR PERMISSION PRIOR TO USING OUR SERVICES. CNI HAS NO LIABILITY OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE ACTS OR OMISSIONS OF TALENT’S AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE OR PURPORTED AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE.

Notice About Minors

The Services are directed to a general audience. We restrict registration for all our Services to individuals age 18 and above (or the age of majority, as determined by the laws of the state in which you reside, whichever is older). If you are under 18 years old (“Minor”), you must have an Authorized Representative register on your behalf. Only Authorized Representatives may create accounts, maintain Account Profiles, and utilize the Services on behalf of Minors. We do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 18 years of age. If you become aware that anyone under 18 has provided us with personal information, please contact us as set forth in Section 9, Contacting Us. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have received information from someone under 18, we will take steps to block that child from accessing our Services and remove that user’s personal information from our systems.

Notice to Authorized Representatives

Each agency, management company and/or individual agent and/or manager engaged by the agency or management company to act on behalf of the Talent (“Talent Representative”), and parents or legal guardians of Minors (collectively referred to as “Authorized Representative”), represent that the Authorized Representative is legally authorized to represent the Talent in connection with the Services and utilize all aspects of the applicable Services on behalf of the Talent, in accordance this Privacy Policy. Authorized Representatives agree to stop using the Services immediately when such authority from Talent is no longer effective. We are not obligated but reserve the right at any time to require evidence of an Authorized Representative’s authority to enter into this Privacy Policy, and act on behalf of Talent in connection with the applicable Services. If we become aware that someone other than an Authorized Representative has established, edited or otherwise modified in any way an Account Profile or Resume for a Talent, we will take steps to terminate the account and remove any corresponding information within our control. Authorized Representatives are solely responsible for their acts or omissions in connection with the Services and indemnify CNI for any claims or liabilities of any kind for their unauthorized or unlawful acts.

**3\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Registering for an Account

You can browse our web or mobile sites without creating an account or telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, in order to create an account on the Services, you (or your Authorized Representative) will be asked to provide us with personal information including your first and last name, email address, username, and a password. If you choose to purchase any of our fee-based Services, you will also be asked to provide credit card information. You must also agree to our Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. 

There are several types of accounts that can be created:

Personal Account

A talent account that is not linked to a CNI registered talent agency or manager.

Personal Account with Manager

A talent account that is linked to a CNI registered manager but is not linked to a CNI registered agency.

Represented Account

A talent account that is linked to a CNI registered talent agency but is not linked to a CNI registered manager.

Represented Account with Manager

A talent account that is linked to both a CNI registered talent agency and CNI registered manager.

Note: A talent account can only be linked to one agency and/or manager at a time.

Filling Out Your Profile

Each member (or its Authorized Representative) will automatically begin to enter basic profile information upon account registration, which will include first and last name, email address, username, and a password. You will be guided to supplement your profile information to include information such as sizes and attributes, representation, union affiliations, professional experience, training, and special skills (“Account Profile”). Certain Account Profile information, including some that is required, is automatically pulled from and displayed in your online Resume. Please do not include information on your Resume that you do not wish others to see. Keep in mind that providing additional information to your Account Profile or Resume can create a better user experience because Industry Professionals have more information about you when casting, searching for talent, etc. Please be aware that the information in your Account Profile may be accessed and modified by you and your Authorized Representative.

Filling Out Your Online Resume

Every account includes an online Resume, which you can choose to display in “Actor Resume” (default) or “Model-Card” format (collectively “Resume”) during the Account Profile completion process. After that, please contact us or your Talent Representative to change the display format selected.

The following information, including some information that is required, is automatically pulled from your Account Profile and displayed on your Resume. You may also add other information directly on your Resume without it appearing in your Account Profile, such as credits. Do not add information to your Resume that you do not want publically available.

Resume information includes:

First, Middle, and Last Stage Name

Union Affiliation

Photos

Attributes

Sizes

Other Representation

Skills

**Contact Information:  **Contact information displayed on your Resume changes based on your member account type as follows:

Personal Account

If entered, your [Casting Billboard](http://cni.lacasting.com/wsdl/webservice.svc/GetCurrentPolicy?siteId=LA&policyType=Privacy%20Policy#billboard) Contact Information Phone 1 and Phone 2 will automatically display as your contact information.

Personal Account with Manager

Your manager’s name and phone number, as registered with CNI, will automatically display as your contact information.

Represented Account (with or without a manager)

Your agency’s name and phone number, as registered with CNI, will automatically display as your contact information.

Promotions and Surveys

If you participate in a promotion, the information collected may be used as set forth in the official rules to notify the winners, award prizes and file winners’ information as required by law. If you participate in a survey, the information we collect from you may be used for the purposes of the survey. Participation in a promotion or survey is voluntary.

Mobile Device Information

If you access our Services through a mobile device, we may collect additional information from you such as your unique device identifier, IP address, language, device’s operating system, and regional location.  We may use this data internally or in conjunction with our third-party service providers or platforms to customize your experience and provide offers that may be relevant to you. Depending on the platform you use to access our Services (e.g. iOS, Android, or Windows Phone), you may be able to control whether we collect location data by adjusting the privacy settings on your wireless device. Please be advised that some features will not be available if you choose to disable the collection of location data. Information obtained from your mobile device in connection with any text or push notification services may include your cell phone number, you carriers name, the date, time and content of your messages and other information you provide to us as part of these Services.

**4\. INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**

Third-Party Tracking and Usage Data

Our third-party analytics providers and we may use a variety of tracking technologies that automatically or passively collect certain information described in this Privacy Policy from your computer, mobile, or other access device whenever you visit or interact with the Services or our advertising (“Usage Data”). Usage Data may be collected from the devices you use to access our Services for a variety of reasons including system administration, to prevent fraudulent activity or improve security, to assess the performance of our Services, and to tell us, for example, the website you were visiting before you came to the Services and the website you visit after you leave the Services, whether you have visited the Services before or if you are a new visitor and to help us identify the features in which you may have the greatest interest. Keep in mind that certain features of our Services are available only through the use of tracking technologies and disabling them may impact the functionality of our Services. We may combine the information collected from you with other information collected through tracking technology. You may find more information about these third party analytics providers, their practices, and your choices on how such Usage Data is collected by clicking here.

Interacting with or Viewing Third-Party Content or Advertisements

Our Services may also contain third-party advertising, links, widgets, or similar code linking to external third-party websites, services or products that we do not control. Therefore, they are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check the privacy policies of those third-party sites or services to determine how the proprietors will utilize your personal information. For example, when you load a page on our Services that has a social plug-in from a third-party site or service such as a Like or Send button, or interact with a third-party ad or link on our Services, you are also loading content from that third-party site. That site may request cookies or use tracking devices. These third parties may use personal and non-personally identifiable information collected from your device (such as IP address or device identifier) to serve you targeted advertising or content. These interactions are subject to the privacy policy of the third-party advertiser. If you would like information about targeted interest-based advertising and your choices not to accept cookies used to track your activities, go to [www.youradchoices.com](http://www.youradchoices.com/) or [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**5\. HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

How We Process Database Information About You

The Services are designed for networking, which enable Industry Professionals to search for you, view your Resume, and to contact you or your Authorized Representative. For example, personal information on your Resume may be visible to casting directors who are searching the database for new talent or Talent Representatives who are searching for their own talent accounts. Please remember that any information you disclose on your Resume may be accessed, used, and stored by Industry Professionals, and redistributed to others in any manner. We attempt to limit access to our searchable database to legitimate Industry Professionals, but we do not do background checks of our members and cannot guarantee who might gain access to the Services. Nor do we have control over how those users may use your personal information. Therefore, there is no expectation of privacy when posting, or otherwise participating in the database Services. You expressly and voluntarily accept and agree to the processing of the information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If at any time you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you must cancel your account by following the instructions in Section 7, Choice and Opt-outs.

We have the right, but not the obligation, to monitor any activity and content associated with the database or other Services. We reserve the right to take action in connection with any content or action we deem to be inappropriate. Please review our Terms for more information regarding your appropriate use of the Services.

Information Posted Through the Services

The Services offer you the opportunity to communicate with Industry Professionals for you and Industry Professionals to share Resumes and other content. For example, if an Industry Professional posts an audition video in which you appear on the Services, it may be viewed by users of the Services and forwarded to others outside the Services. We have no control over what others may post or how those users may use the information. Therefore, you should exercise caution and discretion when using our Services or allowing your Authorized Representative to participate on your behalf.

Personalized URL Link to Your Online Resume

You may opt-in to create a personalized URL link to your online Resume by logging in to your account and clicking “Resume Link” from the Resume drop-down menu. Your online Resume is accessible by members and third parties outside of the Services with whom you have shared the link and web search engines, which are outside of our control.

Talent Scout®

You may opt-in to make your Resume visible to agents and managers searching the CNI database for talent to represent (this functionality is known as “Talent Scout®”). Talent Scout is not available on accounts already linked to a talent agency. To opt-in to Talent Scout®, click on “Representation” under your Profile preferences and select the type(s) of representation you are seeking. To opt-out of Talent Scout®, change your Talent Scout® preference to “Not Seeking Representation.” CNI has no control over how those with access to your Resume use your information.

Casting Billboard®

If you sign up for Casting Billboard, you will be able to submit your Resume to a wide variety of entertainment industry jobs. CNI has no control over how those with access to your Resume or other information you post use your information. If you sign up for Casting Billboard, you agree and opt-in to receive various communications including email notices and telephone calls from members who post on Casting Billboards and access the information you submit on the roles you are interested in.

Multimedia Hosting Service

If you sign up for the Multimedia Hosting Service, Industry Professionals, Authorized Representatives, and we will have access to any video and audio clips that you post.

Authorized Service Providers

We may share your information with authorized third parties such as our vendors who help with our business operations, including the storage and processing of information for the uses listed in this Privacy Policy and providing customer service (“Authorized Service Providers”). For example, financial information you provide will be disclosed to our payment processor to process credit card transactions. In this case, established third-party bank processing agents and distribution institutions handle these transactions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information to process your order. We may disclose information to third parties to verify the authenticity of any financial transaction involving our company or its affiliates or subsidiaries or to update your billing information. We do not store any credit, debit card or financial or bank account information we receive from our payment processor, except for the last four digits of your credit card, card type and billing address for verification purposes.

Co-branded Areas

Certain areas of our Services may be provided to you in association with third parties who provide us specialized content or offer products or services (“Co-Branded Areas”), which identify the third party. If you elect to interact with or register for the products and/or services provided in these Co-Branded Areas, you will either be providing the information you share to us and/or the third party, or we might be providing your personal information directly to the third party. Therefore, your personal information will be subject to this Privacy Policy as well as the privacy policy and practices of such third party. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those third parties, and we suggest you review the respective privacy policies of those third parties to learn more about their privacy practices.

Sharing with Affiliates and Marketing Partners

We may share your personal information and other information we collect from you with our affiliated companies and marketing partners to send you messages about new products, enhancements, special offers and other promotional messages. You may opt-out of receiving any promotional messages from our marketing partners or us by following the instructions in Section 7, Choice and Opt-Outs.

Connecting with Social Networks 

When using our Services in connection with third-party social networking services such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, or Google+ (each and collectively, a "Social Network"), you may have the option to connect your Account or activity on our Services with your Social Network information and activity. If you choose to do this, we may import information from your Social Network account to your Account Profile on our Services. We only import the information you allow to be exported from the Social Network, which is controlled by your privacy settings on that Social Network (“Permitted Social Network Content”). The authentication of your Social Network login credentials is conducted solely by your Social Network. By connecting your Social Network account with our Services and authorizing us to have access to the information, you agree that we may collect, use, and store Permitted Social Network Content across all our Services and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Any information or content you or other users post when participating in social networks, plug-ins or other services that link to our Services becomes public information and is subject to redistribution by third parties or us. Our Services may also provide the ability for you to make announcements regarding auditions or jobs, or invite people to join the Services via email, SMS, or social media platforms. Many of those communications will list your name and email address in the header of the message. Once you have connected with an individual your contact information will be shared with that individual.

Aggregate and Analyze Information

We use aggregate information about our users and other non-personal information to analyze the Services and user behavior. We may combine or supplement the information you give us with information we collect from other sources and use it for any purpose disclosed in this Privacy Policy. For example, as permitted by law, we may collect demographic and other information that is publically available. We also use this information to prepare aggregated reports, which we share with third parties. To learn about our third-party analytics providers’ privacy practices and opt-out options, if any, click [here](http://cni.lacasting.com/wsdl/webservice.svc/GetCurrentPolicy?siteId=LA&policyType=Privacy%20Policy#thirdparty).

Transactional Communications with You and Permitted Third Parties

We use your information to contact you and third parties on your behalf per your request or as otherwise permitted in this Privacy Policy, to send you information about your account or the Services, to respond to you, to provide Services requested by you, for the reasons we disclose to you at the time when we collect your information, or to contact you for purposes authorized or required by law. We may from time to time send you information via text or SMS messages about the Services to the phone number you provide. We do not send promotional messages via text or SMS without your consent.

Mobile/Location Data

When you access the Services on a mobile device, we may use the information collected for any purpose outlined in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may use location information to provide you with location-based services, such as locally based search results, the ability to connect with users of our Services in your area and other personalized content.

Push Notifications

Our application Services may include a function that allows us to use push notifications to send you updates, communications, and other messages about the Services. We do not send promotional messages about other products or services through these push notifications.

Legal Matters; Safety

We may, without your consent, access and disclose your information, any communications sent or received by you, and any other information that we may have about you or your account as may be permitted or required by law or by any government regulatory authority, or to prevent or investigate suspected fraud, violations of our Terms, or activity that appears to us to be illegal or may expose us to legal liability. Any disputes under this Privacy Policy will be resolved in accordance with the binding arbitration process outlined in the Terms. Additionally, we may disclose your information in situations that we believe may involve potential threats to the physical safety of any person or property.

Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets

Our users’ personal information may be one of the assets sold, transferred, or merged if CNI or an affiliated company, brand or business is sold or disposed of as a going concern whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership. We may also disclose information about our users in connection with a commercial transaction where we, or any one of our businesses, is seeking financing, investment, support or funding.

**6\. ACCESSING AND CHANGING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Updating/Changing Your Account Profile Information

Registered members can review and change personal information at any time by logging into their account and clicking on the Profile tab. Date of birth may be changed only by contacting us by telephone at 323-462-8200 ext. 353. Information updated in your Account Profile will automatically update the same information on your Resume. If for any reason you are concerned that any personal information you provided to us is not correct and you cannot change it by accessing your Account Profile or Resume, please contact us at [support@castingnetworks.com](mailto:support@castingnetworks.com). You should promptly update your personal information if it changes or becomes inaccurate.  A Talent Representative may update and change an Account Profile or Resume of a Talent it represents in the same manner as the Talent, except that a Talent Representative may not modify any of Talent’s billing information, login information, email address or date of birth.

**7\. CHOICE AND OPT-OUTS**

Information Sharing with Others

As outlined in Section 5, How We Use and Share Your Information, Resumes are subject to redistribution by Industry Professionals that have access to the information. We have no control over how Industry Professionals may use the Resume or any of the information contained in it. If you do not want your information to be subject to public distribution prospectively, you must cancel your account. Please be aware that any information posted prior to deactivation or cancelation may become public information and we cannot guarantee its removal from our and third-party computer systems. We do not control or assume any responsibility for the information you provide in connection with the Services.

Changing Your Linked Talent Representative

If you would like us to link your account to a Talent Representative different from the one your account is currently linked to, please email us at [change@castingnetworks.com](mailto:change@castingnetworks.com?subject=Representation%20Change%20Request). You must provide the following information:

·       Your name and phone number

·       The Talent Representative you are moving from

·       The Talent Representative you are moving to

We are unable to change your linked Talent Representative over the phone.

Opting In or Out of Talent Scout

To opt-in or out of Talent Scout, or to change your Talent Scout preferences, log into your account, click on the “Profile” tab, and then click “Representation”.

Canceling Your Account

You can cancel your Membership at any point during your subscription term by contacting us by phone at 213-201-8100 Ext. 353 or by e-mailing us at the addresses listed below.  We will cancel your account as soon as possible after resolving any outstanding account issues and in accordance with applicable law.

·     For lacasting.com accounts, email [billing@castingnetworks.com](mailto:billing@castingnetworks.com)

·     For sfcasting.com accounts, email [sfbilling@castingnetworks.com](mailto:sfbilling@castingnetworks.com)

·     For castingnetworks.com accounts, email [nybilling@castingnetworks.com](mailto:nybilling@castingnetworks.com)

When your account is cancelled:

·     You are no longer searchable by Industry Professionals. However, your Resume and any other personal information that you or your Talent Representative previously submitted on casting director projects remains accessible to those casting directors and their clients.

·    Your Profile and Resume are no longer accessible to you or your Talent Representative.

·    Your Resume is no longer accessible to third parties outside of the services.

After canceling your account, we will retain logs and information about you for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you cancel your account, you will not be able to access any of your personal information on our Services.

Transactional Messages

While you are an active member, you may not opt-out of transactional messages regarding your registered account and transactions; however, you may opt-out of receiving such messages via text or SMS. To opt-out of receiving transactional text messages, log into your account, click on Profile and, under the “Text Messages” section, uncheck those texts you no longer wish to receive.

Opting Out of Promotional Messages 

#### Promotional Messages From Us

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may choose to send promotional email messages to you. If you do not wish to receive such messages, you may opt-out by clicking the unsubscribe link included at the bottom of each email we send. To opt out of our “Networker” newsletter, log into your account, click on Profile, and uncheck "Send me Priority Emails..." under the E-Mail Address section. You may also opt-out of the newsletter by sending your opt-out request to [networkerfeedback@castingnetworks.com](mailto:networkerfeedback@castingnetworks.com). Please include your first and last name and the CNI website that you use to log into. Opt-out requests may take up to 10 days to process.

#### Promotional Messages From Our Marketing Partners

To opt-out of promotional email messages from our marketing partners, please email [optout@castingnetworks.com](mailto:optout@castingnetworks.com). Opt-out requests may take up to 10 days to process. 

Opting Out of Push Notifications.

To opt-out of receiving push notifications, you must turn off the push notification function within your mobile device settings.

Timing and Third Parties 

We will endeavor to comply with your requests as soon as reasonably possible, but changes requested of us may not be effective immediately. We are not responsible unless required by law, to inform third parties with whom we have already shared your information of any changes requested pursuant to this section. Nor are we responsible for removing information or causing information to be removed from the databases or records of such entities. 

**8\. IMPORTANT DISCLOSURES**  

Security

CNI uses a third party to process its credit card payment transactions. When you place an order for a paid service at CNI, your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol. We also implement security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However, no security system is 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of any information provided to us in connection with the information that we collect.

Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, known as the "Shine the Light" law, permits California residents to request and obtain a list of what personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the names and addresses of those third parties.

Storage and Retention

Personally identifiable and other information that you provide to us in the course of participating in the Services may be gathered and stored in one or more of our corporate databases. We may retain information from canceled accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, assist with investigations, resolve disputes, analyze or troubleshoot programs, enforce our Terms, or take other actions permitted by law. We may also retain information to prevent re- registration in the event that your account has been suspended or terminated or to create an archival copy of your information, which might be used by us for recordkeeping and internal purposes. We will retain your information for the period of time necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is permitted or required by law.

Jurisdiction and Cross-Border Issues

Our Services are available in the United States and intended for use by account holders located in the United States only. We do not represent or warrant that our Services are appropriate or available for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access the Services do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations. We may limit access to our Services, in whole or in part, to any person, geographic area or jurisdiction we choose, at any time and in our sole discretion. By using our Services and submitting any personal information, you consent to the transfer of personal information to other countries, which may provide a level of data security different from your country of residence. You are also consenting to the application of United States law in all matters concerning the Services.

No Rights of Third Parties

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the Services.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. You agree that we may notify you about material changes in the way we treat personal information by posting a revised Privacy Policy on the Services via a link, with the “Effective Date” posted at the top of the Policy. You should check the Services frequently for updates. By accessing the Services after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to our then-current Privacy Policy.

**9\. CONTACTING US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of CNI, please contact us via email at [support@castingnetworks.com](mailto:support@castingnetworks.com), by phone at 323-462-8200, ext. 353, or via mail at Casting Networks, Inc., Attn: Consumer Services, 3250 Wilshire Blvd. Ste.1800, Los Angeles, CA 90010, USA.

Copyright © 2016 Casting Networks Inc. All rights reserved. 

As of April 25, 2016 

THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS OF ANALYTICS TOOLS

The following is a non-exclusive list of third parties we have chosen to provide us information, reports, and analysis on the usage and browsing patterns of users of the Services. Included are links to their privacy policies and, if applicable, opt-out options to enable you to opt-out of their respective programs.

Google Analytics           [  
Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

New Relic                     [  
Privacy Policy](http://newrelic.com/privacy)

Sisense                         [  
Privacy Policy](http://pages.sisense.com/rs/sisense/images/sisense-privacy-policy.pdf)

EXAMPLES OF TRACKING TOOLS 

Cookies

A cookie is a data file placed on a device when the device is used to visit the Services. We use cookies to collect information for record-keeping purposes and to make it easier to navigate the Services. Cookies are stored on users’ hard drives. We use both “session ID cookies” and “persistent cookies.” Session ID cookies are used to store information while a user is logged into the Services and expire when the user closes his/her browser. Persistent cookies are used to make tasks like logging into the Services easier for returning users by remembering a user’s login information. Persistent cookies stay on a user’s hard drive from one session to the next. Cookies may be used for many purposes including, without limitation, remembering you and your preferences and tracking your visits to our web pages. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a persistent or session cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off such cookies through your browser settings. Every browser is a little different, so refer to your browser’s Help menu for the correct way to modify your cookies. However, cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, please click here. If you choose to disable cookies on your device, some features of the Services may not function properly.

Web Beacons/GIFS

Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as “1×1 GIFs” or “clear GIFs”) may be included in our web pages and messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a web page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes including, without limitation, to count visitors to our Services, to monitor how users navigate the Services, to count how many sent e-mails were actually opened, or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.

Embedded Scripts

An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Services, such as the links you click on. The code downloads temporarily onto the device you use to access Services from our web server or third-party service provider. It is active only while you are connected to the Services, and is deactivated or deleted after that.

HTML 5

We may use HTML5 in some of our Services, including in our mobile website. HTML5 has browser web storage that does not rely on traditional browser cookies. Like Flash cookies, HTML5 cookies are not stored in a browser “cookies” file and, like Flash cookies, can be used to track users across websites. To our knowledge, there is currently no known way for a user of a mobile device to remove HTML5 tracking and storage.

E-tags, Cache Browsers, and Web Logs

Like most standard website servers, we log IP addresses (a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet) and device identifier to improve security, analyze trends, and administer the Services. We may track your movement within the Services, the pages from which you were referred, access times, and browser types. This information may include the browser you are using, the Internet address from which you linked to our Services, the operating system of your computer, the unique IP address of the computer or device identifier of the mobile device that you used to access our Services, and usage and browsing habits. We use this information in the aggregate to gauge the effectiveness, usage, and popularity of our Services, track information for statistical purposes, help diagnose and troubleshoot server malfunctions, analyze trends, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information. We may also use individual information we collect through web logs to send you targeted offers and other communications.
